JINADU MARIAM OLADOYIN

Current Address: Baba Apata House, Abimbola Estate, Tanimowo, Apata Ibadan

E-mail Address: oladoyin.jinadu@gmail.com, mariam.jinadu@yahoo.com

Mobile Phone Number: 08166319469, 08023629088

PERSONAL PROFILE

An assertive, versatile and diligent with 2 years cognate experience in customer Service, Front Desk Office, Roles undertaken in course of experience includes client relationship. To strive for excellence and precision at all time, in all position and circumstances, attaining professional distinction and proficiency. To work with the existing staff and available facilities, contributing the best of my quota, with a view to improving my organization's objective and achieving managerial goals and targets, while profitably building a career ahead.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND/PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND/FROI ESSIONAL QUALITICATION	
Certified Project Manager International Project Management	2016
B.sc in Mass Communication Lagos State University (Second Class Lower Division)	2010 – 2014
Senior Secondary School Certificate Examination Baptist Model High school, Ijegun, Lagos State	2003 – 2009
First Leaving School Certificate Ronik International School, Ejigbo, Lagos State	1996 – 2003

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fortesoft System Limited (NIIT Licensee) Ibadan, Nigeria Academic Counselor/Front Desk Officer Roles and Responsibilities July 2018 till Date

- Handles Phone Inquiries.
- Providing information to Clients that walk in for Inquiries or all those people who will call in the office or visit the office premises.
- Advice the clients on the suitable program.
- Follow up on the Clients.
- Data Entry, weekly & report of sales.
- Meet Personal/team sales targets.
- Handle Complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits and follow up.

Mastared Montessori Schools Customer Relations Officer/Front Desk Officer Roles and Responsibilities

October 2017- July 2018

- Attend to people that walk in for Inquiries or all those people who visit the school premises.
- Handle Complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits
- Be a link between the Parents and school management.
- Register new pupils & staffs on the ACASCOPE Platform.
- Attend to issues on the platform.
- Register Pupils when they pay school fees on the ACASCOPE Platform.

Academic Counselor/Front Desk Officer **Role and Responsibilities**

- Handles Phone Inquiries.
- Providing information to Clients that walk in for Inquiries or all those people who will call in the office or visit the office premises.
- Advice the clients on the suitable program.
- Follow up on the Clients.
- Data Entry, weekly & report of sales.
- Meet Personal/team sales targets.
- Handle Complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits and follow up.

Kogi state House of Assembly **Press Officer (Place of Primary Assignment) Roles and Responsibilities**

May 2015 - September 2016

Writing of the minute and Press release of each sitting proceedings.

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- · Possession of excellent oral and written communication skills to communicate with customers and prospects in writing, via telephone, internet or in person.
- Possession of good marketing strategy.
- Possess excellent organization, time, management, communication skill and Business Management.
- Possession of Strong inquisitive skills.
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Possession of strong computer skills, including experience with Word processing, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point with the confidence and desire to learn new software applications.
- Fluent in English and Yoruba Languages.
- Strong analytical and problem solving skills.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Reading, travelling, meeting people & interacting with them

REFERENCES

Available on request.